♪♪
Honey, I'm reading.
I'm just trying to
make you feel good.
I know, baby, but
this is Hemingway.
I've got to concentrate.
Okay.
Harry?
Hmm?
Should I get my eyes done?
Baby, you've got great eyes.
Really?
- Oh, yeah.
- Look at these lines.
I have lines.
See? Look.
Lines.
Let me see.
Look, right there.
Let me just get a little
closer to you, though.
- Why?
- I want to see.
Mmm.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Joanna, hi.
No. No. No.
Hmm?
No.
Right now?
No problem.
Okay. Bye-bye.
What?
Joanna Wilton wants a workout.
Now?
Well, it seems she
bought this spandex dress
and thinks her thighs
look like tree trunks.
Ah, baby, come on.
I'm a personal trainer.
Mmm. I got to go.
Mmm.
Excuse me.
Hurry home, okay?
Oh, Harry, you've wrecked me.
Oh, honey.
I'm sorry I didn't get a
chance to, you know...
work you out.
That's all right.
I feel very tuned up.
Mmm.
Where you going?
Oh, baby, it's late.
You've been here a
crummy 20 minutes.
Crummy?
Highlight of my day.
Here.
Oh, what is this?
Go ahead, open it.
Tropic of Capricorn,
Henry Miller. Whoa.
It's a first edition.
Wow, this... this
is... this is fantastic.
Read the inscription.
Joanna... how...
how can I thank you?
Oh, baby, come on.
I can't.
No, the book is yours.
Next time, honey, plan to
spend the evening, okay?
Says here you stand
behind your work.
Yes, that's right.
Well, if you had been
standing under it last night,
you would've been as
wet as my rug and my sofa.
- Your new roof is leaking?
- Yes.
- Come on!
- Come on where?
- To my house. Fix my roof!
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'll, uh, send a couple of
men out there in the morning.
In the morning?!
Everyone is gone.
It's the best I can do.
You're going to have to
replace my rug, my sofa
and anything else
that gets ruined.
Your roof will be
fixed, Mr. Matlock.
I employ people who do that.
I also employ people
who will negotiate
a fair settlement
for your furniture.
I even employ
people who will listen
to your complaints with a smile.
I employ those people
so I don't have to do that.
What the hell do you do?
Hire, fire, expand, invest.
Excuse me.
And go to dinner at the
Peachtree Country Club.
It's late, and I'm going.
The roofers will
be there tomorrow.
They better be!
Harry, what are you doing here?
Oh, Brigette.
I need to talk.
Talk... you?
Brigette, please.
Okay, come on.
You know, it's just
that sometimes my
life seems so empty.
I need to settle down.
You should... with Dee Dee.
Oh, I know.
Dee Dee's a great kid.
She's great. It's just that...
I'm in love with you.
Of course, you are.
Ever since I stopped
sleeping with you.
So, who's the new boyfriend?
None of your business.
Oh, baby, baby.
Why didn't I marry you
when I had the chance?
Oh, Harry.
You're a mess.
Get out of here!
Go. Go.
I'll call you.
No, please, please!
"Harry, you're the best.
Love... Joanna."
What the hell?
Joanna, what is this?
- What?
- This!
Oh. Damn.
Who's Harry?
Your personal trainer.
George, your blood pressure.
In our bed!
George, it isn't what it seems.
It's... it's...
You haven't had breakfast.
Harry is going to be
thrilled to see his lighter.
What's with him?
Harry, hi.
It's me.
Maybe you shouldn't
go to work today.
Good. Okay.
25 more.
Twenty-five?
You are full of steam today.
Are you happy?
Yeah.
Wouldn't you be?
Harry is the best.
He is so considerate and loving.
Harry Slade.
Good morning. May I help you?
- Yeah, yeah. Harry Slade.
- Um, do you have an appointment?
Yeah, here's my
appointment right here.
Harry! Harry Slade!
Harry Slade!
Harry!
George?
What are you doing?
I'm looking for Harry Slade.
Harry?
Why?
It's personal.
George, Harry is not here.
So, now, take the gun,
put it back into your
glove compartment,
get into the car
and get out of here
before your blood pressure
goes through the ceiling.
George, go.
Now.
Get me the home
address of a Harry Slade.
He's a personal trainer.
Works in a place called
Morrie's Gym downtown.
Certainly, sir. Right away.
The men didn't
come this morning.
Well, they forgot.
Forgot?!
Look, I'm building a
shopping center in Somerville.
Soon as I can spare
a couple of guys,
I'll send them to your house.
My easy chair got
soaked last night.
I've been sitting
in it for years.
It fits my body like skin.
It's irreplaceable.
What are you gonna do about it?
I didn't call you down here
to talk about your
roof or your easy chair.
I called you down here
because I'm being charged
with first degree murder,
and I want you to defend me,
and I'm willing to pay
you twice your fee.
You damn right you will!
And you'll fix my roof,
and you'll replace my furniture,
and you'll put my
house generally back
in the same order it was
before your lousy workmanship
screwed it up, right?
Right?!
Right.
Sit down.
Now!
Now...
Harry Slade was sleeping
with your wife, right?
Yeah, and charging me for it.
He was a personal trainer.
He made house
calls, he sent bills.
Yesterday, you go down
to the gym where he works,
yelling for him, waving
your gun around,
making a general
jackass out of yourself.
I didn't kill Harry Slade.
You went to his house
and were arrested
standing over his body.
He was dead when I got there.
Shot by your gun.
Anybody could take the gun
out of my glove compartment.
I never locked the car.
Someone wants to
steal it, they can have it.
I'll buy another one.
You're a pretty arrogant
fellow, aren't you?
Yeah.
And you got a lousy temper.
Are you gonna take
this case or not?
You better hope
I'm a better lawyer
than you are a roofer.
♪♪
Uh, hi.
I'm Ben Matlock,
George Wilton's lawyer.
Uh, M-Mr. Matlock,
please, another time.
Dee Dee's terribly distraught.
It's okay, Morrie. Let him in.
Thank you, Morrie,
but I have to...
I have to deal with
this now, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Hi. I'm-I'm Dee Dee Lambert.
I have just a few questions.
I loved Harry.
Go ahead.
You can ask me
anything that you want.
Uh... oh, okay.
Uh, did it seem curious to you
that Joanna Wilton wanted
a-a workout at such a late hour?
No.
Harry would do anything
to keep his clients happy.
He was very dedicated.
Now, he-he left here at 9:00.
What time did he return?
It was, uh, after midnight.
Huh.
Because we-we missed Nightline.
Harry really... He
loved Nightline.
Dee Dee, come on,
you're going to bed.
Come on.
How can you be so cruel?
Well, I'm just... I'm just
trying to get the truth.
Well, that's no reason
to destroy that poor child.
Talk to me.
I'm Morrie.
I was Harry's confidant.
I know everything.
- Well.
- Can we sit down?
Well, there's nowhere to sit
unless you want to
get your hind end wet.
Well... what do you
want to talk about?
Harry Slade.
Do we have any leads?
Oh, well, I don't know.
Uh, Dee Dee... that's
his, uh, live-in girlfriend...
Said that he left the house
at-at 9:00 and
didn't get back till,
uh, midnight, after midnight.
And-And, uh,
Joanna, though, said
that he got to her house,
uh, around 10:15 and left...
Hmm.
Uh, by 11:00, and it's
only a ten minute drive.
Hmm. So it leaves an hour before
and an hour after
unaccounted for.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh!
Oh, oh. Oh, yeah.
Ah.
When are they
gonna fix your roof?
Well, they were
supposed to be here today,
but guess what?
Mm.
Roofers don't work in the rain.
Come on, Brigette.
George, you've only
been here 30 seconds.
You're gonna be
gone in 12 minutes.
I spent the night in jail,
half a million dollars on bail,
I got a company to run...
Yes?
What the hell
- are you doing here?
- George,
I'm here trying to find out
about the women in Harry's life.
What the hell are
you doing here?
You're supposed to be
climbing my roof, not her.
Well, I was...
Did you say the
women in Harry's life?
Brigette.
George, listen to me.
Harry was a long, long time ago.
Joanna is one thing, but you.
I loved you!
And I love you.
Yeah, me and Harry
and God knows who else.
Pack up your stuff
and get out of here!
- George! -MATLOCK: Hold it.
- And leave the jewelry.
- Hold it!
- You heard me. Come on. Get out.
Hold it!
What?!
She's not going anywhere.
You are.
And not a word
of this to anybody.
I own this house. She's out.
Are you out of your mind?
If one word gets out
about Harry having an affair
with your wife
and your mistress,
the D.A. will kill us fast.
You got that?
George...
- Okay? Okay?
- Yeah, sure.
Great!
Just great.
Something good finally
happens in my life.
Why did you have to
tell him about Harry?
Well...
the way I hear it,
Harry's over here a lot.
Morrie told you.
Yeah.
Doesn't it stand to reason
that George finds out
about you and Harry,
he's gonna get
mad and put an end
to this little arrangement
pretty quick?
Harry's and my romance
was over long ago.
We were friends.
Is that what you
were talking about
when he stopped by here
on his way back from
Joanna's that night?
Morrie knew about that?
No.
Lucky guess.
What happened?
Nothing.
He, um... He was here for
about 45 minutes talking.
Then George pulled up.
Harry went out the back, okay?
Okay.
When Harry was
shot, you were, uh...
At Mason's department store.
Shopping.
Hmm? Alone?
Mm-hmm, yes.
You didn't speak to a clerk?
No. I-I... I didn't
buy anything.
No. Uh, we mistresses...
We-we window-shop a lot.
We don't have to
go home to fix dinner.
Well... whichever
way this turns out,
quite a few people are
gonna have to spend
a lot of time in church.
Behind you and lift
for ten counts. One.
And two. Quicker!
Three. Come on, go for it! Four.
Mom?
- What?
- And five. Remember to lift.
Mom, uh, this is Miss Thomas.
She's one of George's attorneys.
I have a few questions
if you don't mind.
Come on. Ten. And...
Bobbie.
I want to hear this.
You have kids?
Not yet.
Bobbie's from my first marriage.
When you have kids young,
you can't lie about your age.
It drives me crazy.
Oh, I imagine.
You told the police Harry
got to the house at 10:15.
The guesthouse. Yeah.
Oh.
Um... why the guesthouse?
Miss Thomas?
Where else would
I entertain Harry?
Oh.
Um, Harry left his
house around 9:00.
Did he say what
took him so long?
No. And I didn't
waste time asking.
Oh.
Um, at the time of the murder...
Where was I?
Miss Thomas, Harry
and I got along fine.
We understood each other.
Now, if it was my
husband who'd been shot,
I could understand your
asking me these questions.
I beg your pardon?
George is slime.
I should have realized it
when his attorney showed up
at our wedding rehearsal...
with a prenuptial contract.
But I was naive.
I had no reason to kill Harry.
See, rumor has it that
you'd been promising
to back him in his own gym.
I was thinking about it.
But not coming up with the
cash, so maybe Harry got tired
of being strung
along and threatened
to tell your husband
about the two of you.
Wouldn't it have
just been easier
for me to tell George
and let him kill Harry?
I suppose you have an alibi
for the time of the murder.
No.
I don't need one.
I didn't kill Harry.
Hi.
Got your message. What's up?
Well, we're keeping
an eye on Brigette Laird.
She said she was shopping at
Mason's when Harry was shot,
but they're closed on Mondays.
What about the wife?
She's an ice queen,
and she doesn't have
an alibi or a motive.
Well, not that we know of.
We can't underestimate Harry.
He was... I know. Amazing.
Oops.
Here we go.
♪♪
Oh... Well, now what?
Let me have your purse.
- Really?
- Yeah, okay.
Uh, sir, sir, excu-excuse me.
Uh, that nice-looking lady
that just pulled up in, in
the, in the Mercedes there...
Her name is,
uh... Bri-Br... yeah,
Brigette Laird.
Uh, she dropped her purse
when she got on the elevator.
I wondered if you could
tell me where she's going.
Ms. Laird's purse was
black patent leather.
Oh.
You want to know
where she went with it,
it's going to cost
you a Jackson.
A Jackson?
As in Andrew... 20 big ones.
Oh, 20, uh, 20, uh, dollars.
Uh... uh...
649.
- May I help you?
- Uh, y-yeah, well, I-I wonder if...
I'm ready, Alex.
Ms. Laird.
I don't believe it.
You followed me?
You know them?
Mason's was closed
the day Harry was shot.
All right, all right, I
was here with Alex.
- You and him?
- No.
We're friends, we went
to high school together,
he married my cousin.
I'm a painter.
Brigette is my subject.
Well, why didn't
you just tell us
you were here
in the first place?
Because I'm Alex's nude subject,
and if George
were to find that out,
I would have become
Alex's homeless nude subject.
Lot of people gonna have
to go to a lot of churches.
Mr. Matlock, I'm Bobbie,
George Wilton's
stepdaughter. Hi.
What's up?
Well... this is kind of hard.
I mean, uh, this is a secret.
Secrets have a way of
coming out in a murder trial.
Well, that's what I'm afraid of.
Uh...
it's about where Harry was for
an hour before he saw my mom.
Yeah?
He was with me.
He was with you?!
You... you and Harry?
I'll be 22 in January.
This guy was truly amazing.
Yeah... I thought so.
Well, d-does anybody else know?
No.
Does anyone else have to know?
Well, th-tha-that depends.
Uh, where were you
when Harry was shot?
I was with my mom.
Y-You can ask her.
No, your mother says
she doesn't have an alibi.
Oh, Mr. Matlock, my
mother is protecting me.
From what?
Well, I was convicted
of shoplifting.
- Shoplifting?
- Yeah.
Um, my shrink says that I do
it, um, because I need attention.
It's the byproduct
of low self-esteem.
I come from a
dysfunctional home.
Your shrink told the judge that?
Yeah.
I even cried.
And then the judge says
that I'm spoiled rotten
and he sentences me
to community service
at Betty Harding's
Child-Care Center.
So that's where you
were... At Betty Harding's?
Yeah, my mom takes me.
We were there
when Harry was shot.
Oh.
You were both there...
You're sure of that?
Yeah.
Oh, I know, I know.
Mom's kind of bitchy.
She's had crummy luck with men.
But she tries to be a mother.
Sometimes.
Ben.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Did you get anything on Dee Dee?
A possible motive...
I mean, she was the spurned
lover here... and no alibi.
Ben, she couldn't
have killed a fly.
- You don't think so?
- Do you?
I don't know.
What about Joanna?
She got herself an alibi.
- She did?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Harry was having
an affair with... Guess.
I don't know.
She's going to be 22.
Isn't everybody?
I can't guess.
- Stepdaughter.
- I don't know.
George Wilton.
- Bobbie?
- Yeah.
Yeah, the wife, the girlfriend,
now the stepdaughter.
The D.A. is going to
have a ball with this one.
If I didn't hate him so much,
- I'd feel sorry for the son of a...
- There you are.
Hey, what say, George?
Uh, how we doing?
Oh, pretty good, pretty good.
My men get to your house yet?
Oh, no, no.
Well, we'd better go inside.
Thank you.
Ben, what are we going to do?
About what?
About the case.
Oh, we'll try to pick a jury and
hope there aren't too many women
who were amazed by
the late Harry Slade.
Ah, yes,
there it is... Jason
Langer's birthday.
Ah, Bobbie and Mrs.
Wilton were definitely here.
I remember greeting
them at the curb
right where you're parked.
Mrs. Wilton needed my help
- with Jason's present.
- Ah.
What time was that?
Oh, 10:00, maybe
a little bit after.
Hey, that's nice.
Looks like a jungle.
Hey, mister, look.
Uh-huh-huh.
That's nice, that's nice.
Mr. Matlock, I am so sorry.
Oh, that's all right.
I'll...
Robert, we don't touch other
people with paint on our hands.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Good, good, good.
Now, you were saying...
Do you remember what time
Mrs. Wilton and her daughter left?
They left at 1:00.
And Mrs. Wilton waited
here the whole time?
Uh, upstairs.
She was doing some
routine to an exercise tape.
Some of us have time to, uh...
be obsessed with
maintaining our youth.
- Was she alone?
- Yes.
You're not gonna get me.
Jason, watch where you're going.
Is it possible that
she could have left
and come back
without being seen?
Douglas, Roland,
we have to share.
I'm sorry, you were saying...
Uh, well, you're busy.
May we speak with
some of the other staff?
Oh, please, be my guest.
Katie, don't put Play-Doh
up your nose, sweetie.
Ooh...
Did I tell you I
once taught school?
You did?
I hated it.
Oh.
So no one actually saw
Joanna at the time of the murder?
No one saw her leave either.
Well... Aw... What'd
I do to get a ticket?
I didn't do anything
to get... a ticket.
Yes.
Mr. Matlock, hello.
- Hi.
- Come in.
Oh, everything looks different.
Yes.
I'm trying to become
more spiritual.
Oh.
How about some tea?
I have mint, chamomile, comfrey.
Oh, no, thanks, I...
- You sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Ever since you called,
I've been thinking
about the night of the...
- you know.
- Murder?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
The only thing I can remember
is that that night,
when Harry got home,
he was really excited about
this book Joanna had given him.
What book?
That's the thing... I can't
figure out what happened to it.
It's gone.
Are you sure?
I looked everywhere for it.
I know it's, um, it's just
a material possession,
but... it belonged to Harry
and... now it's gone.
Yeah, well, I-I don't think
this is a very good idea.
I got no choice.
You don't know anything
about roofing, Ben.
I bet I know as much about it
as George "I'll Be
There Tomorrow" does.
Oh, Ben, be careful.
Ms. Thomas, does Mr. Matlock
know he's supposed to be here?
Of course, Your Honor.
He's just been delayed...
Oh, thanks.
I apologize, Your Honor.
It took me ten minutes
to get up the stairs
and then I just
had to wait there
till somebody opened
the door and then...
You are excused, Mr. Matlock.
We'll proceed as soon as
you've caught your breath.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh, Your Honor, could I
have a moment with my client?
All right, five minutes.
What the hell happened to you?
I fell off my roof.
I was trying to fix it.
It was leaking.
The man who said he'd
fix it lied to me, cheated me,
and now has crippled me.
Well, that's great.
Jury will feel sorry for you.
George,
you're going to have to
get yourself another lawyer.
What?
Well, I just realized I
have a conflict of interest.
See, I plan to sue
you for damages,
and I can't represent
you at the same time.
It's a conflict of interest.
You can't drop me now.
Where the hell am I going
to get another attorney?
I don't know,
but I can't be suing you
and representing you.
I mean, it just isn't done.
It's a conflict of interest.
Look, I-I-I'll pay, I-I'll pay,
I'll pay if you don't sue me.
I'll pay for all the damage
done by your leaky roof.
Y-You don't understand.
There's the damage to my house,
there's the stress that I
have suffered during all this,
and now-now my medical bills,
and we're talking...
$250,000 minimum.
And you don't want to go,
you don't want to go
through all that, so...
I'm just gonna have to
drop you and sue you.
I'll pay, I-I'll pay.
Just don't sue me and
don't drop me now, okay,
because you're the
only hope I have.
Uh, Mrs. Wilton,
how would you describe
your relationship,
uh, to the defendant?
He's my husband.
Is it-is it a good marriage?
How do you mean?
Well, uh, d-do you love him?
Uh, have you been faithful?
Objection... relevancy.
Relevancy?
The state has accused my client
of killing Harry Slade
in a jealous rage.
How could testimony
about his relationship
with the object
of that jealousy...?
Overruled.
- Mr. Matlock...
- Thank you.
Would you repeat the question?
"Is it a good marriage?
"Do you love him?
Have you been faithful?"
Well, let's see.
It isn't, I don't, I haven't.
Huh.
Why don't you divorce him?
It's no secret... money.
Now, a prenuptial
agreement keeps you
from your husband's money
if you divorce and his will
specifically disinherits
you upon his death.
So I guess you'll
have to stay married
if you wish to continue
the life to which you have
been so accustomed, won't you?
So it would seem.
Of course, if he's found guilty
and goes to prison, as his wife,
that kind of puts you in charge
of his business and his money,
doesn't it?
Objection... relevancy.
It's also argumentative,
Your Honor.
I'll sustain the objection.
The-the night before the murder,
uh, you, I guess you could say,
oh... uh, rendezvoused
with Harry out there in
the guesthouse, didn't you?
- That's true.
- Yeah, and you'd been doing that
out there in the guesthouse
for what, four or five
months, hadn't you?
Yes.
But you never met with him
in the main house, did you?
Never.
I'm not a tacky
woman, Mr. Matlock.
Uh, defense enters exhibit "H."
Would you examine
this and tell us what it is?
It's a gold cigarette
lighter I gave to Harry.
Read the inscription.
"Harry, you are the best.
Love, Joanna."
Your husband
found this, didn't he,
and discovered
your affair with Harry?
Yes.
Where'd he find it?
Um, in the... our bedroom.
I thought you said you never
met him in the main house.
- I guess I was mistaken.
- Uh-huh.
Harry was an hour late
meeting you that night, wasn't he?
Yes.
Who else was in
the house at the time
who could have been
in the master bedroom?
I don't know.
Your daughter Bobbie was
at home that night, wasn't she?
I don't remember.
I can subpoena
Bobbie's testimony.
No.
No, Bobbie... Bobbie
was in the house.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
And Harry's lighter having
shown up in the master bedroom,
you knew he was
with Bobbie, didn't you?
Did it make you mad?
Very.
I'm her mother.
Didn't it make you so angry
that you suddenly saw this whole
sordid mess as an opportunity
to get out of the marriage
and keep the money?
Isn't that why you
shot Harry Slade
and-and framed your husband?
That's not true.
I couldn't have killed Harry.
I was with my daughter
when Harry was killed.
O-On the day of the
murder, September 10?
Yes.
I take her to Betty
Harding's Child-Care Center
every Monday from 10:00 to 1:00.
She works there.
Oh, she works there?
Yes.
Wh-What do you do
while she's working?
I exercise upstairs.
Alone?
If I wanted to sweat in
public, I would join a gym.
Harry trained me at home.
- Yeah.
- Yes, I was alone.
So, so how abou... how
about th-the day of the murder?
Di-Did anybody see you
between 10:00 and 1:00?
Maybe, maybe
not, I-I don't know.
Let's see, let's see now.
Harry was killed, oh,
sometime around 12:20.
That would have given you
plenty of time to have
left and come back,
wouldn't it?
Well, I never left.
Never, Mrs. Wilton?
Never, Mr. Matlock.
Mm-hmm.
Did you drive your
Jaguar that day?
Yes.
Big blue Jaguar,
license plate EGH6G5?
That's the one.
Where'd you park?
I don't know where I parked.
Of course you do.
It was... Remember, it was
Jason Langer's birthday.
Does that jog your memory?
That's right, I had
a present for him.
It was a big stuffed animal.
I parked right in front
so I could carry it in.
They have street
cleaning in front
of the Child-Care Center on
Mondays from 12:00 to 1:00,
and they're very strict
about their parking tickets.
I got one.
Did you?
Well, I guess I must have.
I really don't know.
George's office
manager pays all of those.
Uh-huh.
I'm-I'm showing you
a... a computer printout,
uh, subpoenaed for the trial
from the Violations Bureau,
and we'll-we'll mark this
defense exhibit "J," yeah.
This is-this is a list of
license plate numbers
of all the vehicles cited for
parking violations on the street
in front of the Child-Care
Center on the day of the murder.
Now, look at it carefully.
And, uh, your blue Jaguar,
license plate EGH, uh...
6G5, is not on that list, is it?
No, I-I don't know
why I didn't get a ticket.
It's because you left before
the street cleaners got there.
You drove to your husband's
parking lot, took the gun
out of his glove compartment
where you knew he kept it,
went over to Harry's house
and shot him dead, didn't you?
- No.
- You shot him,
but before you left the house,
you took the first edition
of Tropic of Capricorn
that you had given him
the day before, didn't you?
I have never been
to Harry's house ever.
You're in court now.
You have to tell the truth.
This is all ridiculous.
You can't prove any of
the things that you're saying.
For the record and for you...
this officer...
thank you... is
handing me a book
and I'm handing
you the same book
for identification.
Now, examine that.
Tropic of Capricorn
by Henry Miller.
That's the same book
you gave Harry, isn't it?
Read the inscription.
Okay, I'll read it.
"To Harry," you are the best.
Love, Joanna."
Any idea where it was found?
Let the record
show that this officer,
pursuant to a search warrant,
retrieved this book from
the courthouse parking lot.
It was found
in the locked trunk
of a blue Jaguar...
License plate EGH6G5...
A car belonging to
Mrs. Joanna Wilton.
Ladies and
gentlemen of the jury,
have you reached a verdict?
We find the defendant
George Wilton not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury.
Court is adjourned.
You are the best.
You remember our little
meeting out in the hall?
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
And we have an agreement?
Yeah, yeah, we
have an agreement.
Thank you, Ms. Thomas.
Congratulations.
Well, I hope they have
a good life together.
I guess she still loves him.
Some women have
incredible patience.
Yeah.
Wait till she asks
him to fix her roof.
www.tvsubtitles.net